- 어서 와
- 왔니?
Cereal killer.
시리얼킬러구나
Cereal killer?
시리얼킬러?
딴 사람들이 종일 떠들어도 내가
아침에 하는 헛소리를 못 따라와
Hey, come on, I say more
dumb things before 9 a.m...
...than most people say all day.
What?
왜?
I can't find anything that I wanna eat.
Everything makes me nauseous.
도무지 먹고 싶은 게 없어
뭘 봐도 속이 메슥거려
누가 임신이 누워서
떡 먹기래? 우, 떡!
I'm telling you, being pregnant
is no piece of cake. Oh, cake!
No.
아냐
어떡하니
Honey, I'm sorry.
됐어, 이게 무슨 냄새지?
What is that smell?
It's coming from the bathroom.
화장실에서 나는 듯한데
Pregnancy does give you
some weird cravings.
임산부들 식성은 참 묘해
- 왜?
- 나야, 피비
It's me. It's Phoebe. Listen, there's
something in here I want to eat.
여기 내가 먹고 싶은 게 있어
이게...
What smells so good?
무슨 냄새야?
-ls it the shampoo? It's guava.
-No.
샴푸 아닐까?
구아바거든
아냐
Wait.
오, 잠깐!
내 볼로냐 샌드위치?
Is it my bologna sandwich?
맞아, 바로 그거야
Yes. Yes. Yes.
I can't believe it. The baby wants bologna.
The baby wants meat. I can't eat meat.
아기가 소시지를 원하나 봐
어떡해, 난 고기 못 먹는데
Wait!
잠깐만!
혹시 피클 아냐?
Maybe it's the pickle!
The One With the Fake Party
What are you writing?
뭘 쓰는 거야?
Joshua's coming in tomorrow, and since
I don't have the guts to ask him out...
내일 조슈아가 오는데
난 만나자고 할 배짱이 없잖아
코트를 사러 오니까
주머니에 넣어두려고
...I'm gonna sell him a coat
and put this note in the pocket.
- 그래?
- 안돼
"Joshua, give me a call sometime.
Guys like you...
조슈아, 전화 한번 주세요
당신 같은 사람은...
...never go out of style."
유행에 뒤지는 일이 없죠
What did you throw away?
버린 건 무슨 내용인데?
-Hi, guys.
-What have you guys been up to?
- 어서 와
- 안녕하세요
어디 갔다 와?
We went to see a collection of
Victorian doorknobs at the museum.
박물관에서 빅토리아시대
문고리 전시회 구경했어
Without me?
나만 쏙 빼고?
My uncle dragged us there,
but it turned out to be really interesting.
삼촌한테 끌려간 건데
생각보다 재미있었어요
맞아
They were so ornate and beautiful.
Look at that.
정말 화려하고 예뻤어요
이걸 봐요
I don't know how museums work in England,
but here, you're not supposed to take stuff.
영국은 어떤지 모르지만
그런 거 들고 오면 안돼요
기념품가게에 있던 거예요
경비가 너무 허술하던데요?
I got it from the gift shop.
They have really lax security there.
It's a joke.
농담이에요
차 더 하실래요?
Anyone for more tea?
No, just me then.
그냥 해본 소리예요
Hey, Ringo.
이봐, 빙고
Every time Emily's around, you talk
like her. Would you please cut it out?
에밀리 볼 때마다
흉내 내는 거 하지 마
I think you like it.
좋아하는 줄 알았는데?
I think you can't resist me when I do it.
내 농담을 거부할 수 있나?
You want to eat me up
like a cream "pumpy."
날 한입에 먹어치우고 싶지?
-What?
-All right, look, I don't know all the words.
- 뭐?
- 다른 단어는 몰라
Right. I've got to be off.
I'll see you. Bye-bye, then.
난 가봐야겠네요
그럼 안녕
Bye-bye, then.
You guys seem to be having a good time.
두 사람 꽤 잘돼가네?
She is amazing,
and she's so much fun.
정말 괜찮은 여자야
얼마나 재미있는데
And you know what?
When I'm with her, I'm fun!
같이 있으면 나까지
재미있는 사람이 돼
I do things like run off to Vermont...
가령 버몬트까지 날아갔고
너희들 그 문고리 봤어?
...and you guys saw the doorknob.
헬기 조종강습에도 등록했어
I even signed up
for helicopter classes.
에밀리는 이틀 후에 가니까
안 나가도 돼
She's leaving in two days.
I don't have to do it.
이틀 후에? 속상하겠다
Two days?
You must be bummed.
런던으로 돌아가야 한대
She's got to go back to London, but
I've been prepared for this from the start.
하지만 난 처음부터 각오했어
2주밖에 없다는 건 둘 다 알았지
We both knew we had two weeks together,
and then that's it.
Hey, that's what all
my relationships are like.
거의 내 연애방식이다
저 경우는 두 사람 다
2주뿐이란 걸 알았어
Yes, but in Ross' case,
they both know in two weeks that's it.
-Pheebs!
-Hello. Hello.
- 피비
- 어서 와
- 아가야, 안녕
- 됐어, 그만해
No, I know. Yeah.
So the baby is totally craving meat.
아기가 고기를 너무 좋아해
아까 한 번 속여 보려고
콩 햄버거를 먹었거든?
I tried tricking it, and I made it a soy burger,
so that maybe it'd think it was getting meat.
근데 다 게워냈어
And I got nauseous.
원래 콩버거는 개밥이니까
Maybe that's because soy burgers suck.
But I'm no obstetrician....
난 산부인과 의사가 아니지만
Being pregnant is hard on your tummy.
먹는 게 너무 고역이야
그래도 임산부라 그런지
얼굴에 홍조가 돈다
At least you got that
cool, pregnant-lady glow.
땀이야, 아침내 토해봐
안 번들거리고 배기나
That's sweat. You throw up all morning,
you'll have that glow too.
Okay.
- 볼까요?
- 이 트렌치코트 맞죠?
-Here's that trench coat that you wanted.
-Great.
네, 좋아요
- 아주 편하군요
- 네
It's comfortable.
You could really
flash somebody in this.
뭔가 보여줘도 멋지겠는데?
No. They don't want you to put your hands in
the pockets until you are out of the store.
매장 밖으로 나가기 전에는
주머니에 손 넣으면 안돼요
Why not?
왜죠?
저기, 그러니까...
이런 손님들이 많아서...
Well, because...
...we get a lot of
They ruin it for everybody.
- 몰지각한 사람들
- 맞아요
I know.
I wore that sweater
on a date last night.
그 캐시미어 스웨터
어제 데이트할 때 입었어요
아내와 헤어진 후
처음 하는 데이트였죠
It was the first date
since the divorce.
Congratulations.
So do you love her?
축하해요, 그 여자 사랑해요?
아뇨, 괜찮은 여자지만
난 아직 준비가 안됐나 봐요
She's nice,
but it made me realize...
...I'm just not ready to be dating.
그렇군요
That's interesting.
그거 정말 재미있네요
이봐요
그게 뭐죠?
-What was that?
-Just an anti-theft device.
도난방지장치예요
Then what's this?
그럼 이건?
그것도 필요해요, 이런 건
도둑이 찢어버리면 그만이죠
You need that too, because
a thief could just tear this up.
We have to have a party in five minutes,
so everybody cancel your plans.
오늘밤 파티야
5분 후에 시작이니까
약속은 모두 취소해
What's going on?
- 무슨 소리야?
- 왜 그래?
에밀리 깜짝 송별파티인데
실은 조슈아를 위해서야
We have to have
a bon-voyage party for Emily.
But it's actually for Joshua.
That sucks. Nobody's ever thrown me
a bon-voyage-Emily party.
난 '에밀리표 송별파티'
한 번도 못 받아봤다
데이트할 준비가 안 돼있대
He said he's not ready to date.
밖에서 만나려면 파티에
초대하는 수밖에 없었어
So I had to invite him to a party
if I wanted to see him outside of work.
그 남자를 유혹할
절호의 기회야
And now I have created
the perfect opportunity to seduce him.
나도 조슈아 만나서
경고를 해주고 싶지만
As much as I'd like
to meet Josh and warn him...
에밀리는 와서 인사만 하고
나와 함께 외출할 거야
...Emily and I won't be here.
She's gonna come by to say goodbye...
...and then I've got a special evening
planned. Sorry. No party.
오늘밤엔 특별한 계획이 있어
미안하지만 파티는 안 되겠다
어어?
-Hello?
-Surprise!
- 안녕하세요
- 놀랐죠?
Surprise!
놀랐죠!
No one's thrown me
a surprise party before.
깜짝 파티는 난생 처음이에요
Well, it was all Ross' idea.
전부 로스가 생각해냈대요
You're so sweet.
자상한 사람
And I'm so surprised.
진짜 놀랐어요
You didn't know?
정말 눈치 못 챘어?
Why are you over here
if Joshua's over there?
조슈아는 저기 있는데
넌 왜 여기 있는 거야?
좀 비싸게 보이려고
I'm trying to play hard-to-get.
Quick! He's looking.
Say something funny.
어머, 이쪽 본다
웃기는 얘기해봐
Like what?
어떤 거?
What's so funny?
뭐가 그렇게 웃겨?
I said, "Like what?"
난 '어떤 거' 그랬거든?
Now that's a thinker.
무지 어렵네
This playing-hard-to-get thing
is not working.
이 작전은 전혀 먹히질 않아
그 체리 좀 줘봐
Hand me those cherries.
- 좋아
- 그래
보자
- 저예요
- 네
-Care for a cherry?
-No, thanks.
체리 드려요?
- 됐어요
- 그래요?
난 혀로 체리줄기를
묶을 수 있는데
I can tie one of these into a knot
using just my tongue.
You okay?
괜찮아요?
You all right?
됐어요?
곧 나가야겠어
We should probably get going soon.
But the party's just getting started.
파티는 이제 시작인 걸?
15분 후에 포시즌스에서
간단하게 한잔하고
We have to be at The Four Seasons
for drinks in 15 minutes.
저녁은 플라자호텔이야
Then The Plaza for dinner.
So why did you plan a party
at the same time?
왜 같은 시간에
파티를 열었어?
그런 게 아니지
미국식 깜짝 파티는 원래 짧아
놀랐지! 깜짝이야! 빠이빠이!
Actually, American surprise parties
are very short.
It's usually, "Surprise!"
Then, "My God, I'm so surprised. Bye!"
Ross, I'm having such a great time.
지금도 재미있는 걸?
Your sister told me that
you used to dress up like old ladies...
자긴 어렸을 때 할머니 변장하고
가짜 다과회를 열곤 했다면서?
...and host make-believe
tea parties.
Monica said that, did she?
모니카가 그런 얘기도 했어?
Did she tell you
that when she was little...
참, 그리고 얘가 어렸을 때
...she was partially responsible for
new legislation...
그네 줄의 강도를 규정하는
법안제정에 일조한 거 알아?
...regulating the strength
of swing sets?
와, 그 위에 뭘 얹을 거야?
Then what are you going
to put on top of that?
-A little salami.
-Oh, yeah.
살라미?
저런, 좋지
What goes on top of the salami?
살라미 위엔 뭘 얹을 건데?
Pastrami.
- 파스트라미
- 그래, 맞아...
You're a genius.
넌 천재야
Give me a hand with the zipper.
- 누가 좀 도와줘
- 그래
Up!
올려!
-You changed?
-I decided I needed my lucky dress.
- 옷 갈아입었어?
- 그래, 내 행운의 드레스야
-Lucky means more cleavage?
-lt does for me.
- 행운의 젖고랑이 아니고?
- 동의합니다
어쩜 저렇게 귀엽니
확 끌어안고 키스하고 싶다
Look at him!
He's so cute.
I just want to grab him and kiss him.
내 맘 안 들키고
키스할 순 없나?
How could I kiss him
without him knowing I like him?
방법을 알려줄까?
브라를 벗어
I know how you can get him.
Take off your bra.
What?
뭐?
- '풋루즈'에서 봤거든
- '플래시댄스'야
-This scene in Footloose
-Flashdance.
맞아
-Yeah. With that plumber girl?
-A welder.
- 여자 배관공인데...
- 용접공이야
Were you, like, in the movie?
너 그 영화에 출연했냐?
She takes off her bra under the shirt
and pulls it out the sleeve.
아무튼 브라를 옷 속에서 풀어
소매로 꺼내는 장면이 있거든
Very sexy. And classy.
엄청 섹시하고 우아해
-Or you could use mistletoe.
-It's not Christmas.
겨우살이 밑에 있으면
키스할 수 있다잖아
크리스마스도 아닌데?
- 병 돌리기는 어때
- 어린애니?
-Spin-the-bottle.
-He's not 11.
Thank you so much for this.
It was so thoughtful of you.
다들 마음 써줘서
정말 고마워요
왜요? 벌써 가려구요?
You're leaving?
그래, 계획이 있어서
-We have something we have to get to.
-I'm gonna take off too.
- 안돼
- 나도 이만 가볼게요
You can't leave yet.
You have to stay.
지금 가면 내가 서운하죠
진짜 멋진 순서가 남아있는데
We've got the whole
big thing planned.
What big thing?
멋진 순서라니
Spin-the-bottle works like this:
I spin the bottle.
이렇게 하는 거예요
병이 돌다 건터를 향해 멈췄죠?
그럼 건터한테 키스하는 거예요
Lands on Gunther,
so I would have to kiss Gunther.
All right.
됐죠?
Who wants to go first?
누가 먼저 할래요?
I'll go.
- 내가 할게요
- 좋아요
Welcome to America.
미국에 잘 왔어요
좋아
Oh, my God!
- 어머!
- 세상에!
Two in a row!
You gotta use your tongues now.
연속 두 번이네
그럼 혀를 써야 돼
- 좋아요
- 에밀리 차례예요
All right.
What are the odds?
뭐가 이래?
됐어, 그만
That's enough!
이젠 다른 사람이 하자
Let's let someone else play.
If you didn't want to play,
then why'd you come to the party?
놀기 싫으면 파티엔 왜 왔냐
All right, I'll go.
좋아, 내가 할게
Somebody loose.
누구는 각오해라
Story of my life.
이게 내 팔자야
잘해
Story of my father's life.
우리 아버지 팔자야
내 차례다!
Okay, my turn.
어머나!
Look at that!
이럴 수가, 세상에...
Oh, my God.
The baby just kicked!
방금 아기가 찼어!
괜찮아, 또 찰 거야
It's okay. It's okay.
If it kicked once, it'll kick again!
Everybody just remember
where they were sitting.
좋아, 각자 자기 자리
확실히 기억해둬
It was a bug.
벌레예요
It doesn't matter
how much I'm craving it.
아무리 식욕이 당겨도 고기는
안 먹어, 잔인한 살생이니까
You know why I'm never gonna eat meat?
Because it's cold-blooded murder.
Okay.
알았어
There's a Phoebe on my sandwich!
내 샌드위치에
피비가 들어있어
What are you doing?
- 너 지금 뭐하는 거야
- 어쩔 수가 없어
I can't help it!
I need the meat!
The baby needs the meat.
고기를 먹어야겠어
아기도 고기가 먹고 싶대
You know when you're dating someone...
이왕 애인 몰래 바람피우려면
끝내주는 상대를 골라야겠지?
...and you don't want to cheat
unless it's with someone really hot?
Totally.
- 물론이지
- 그럼 좋아
This is the same kind of deal.
이것도 같은 이치야
이왕 나쁜 짓 하려면...
If you're gonna do something wrong...
...do it right.
제대로 해야지
-I'll be back in a minute.
-Okay.
- 금방 올게요
- 네
정말...
What are you doing to me?
이게 무슨 짓이야
I'm trying to get Emily out of here,
and you keep talking to her...
우리 지금 외출할 건데
계속 에밀리를 웃기고 있잖아
...being all interesting
and making her laugh.
I don't want you to be funny anymore.
지금부터 웃기지 마
Rachel wants me to be funny,
you don't want me to be funny.
레이첼은 웃기라고 하고
넌 웃기지 말라고 하고
From now on, I'm gonna be funny
sometimes, and not funny others.
이제부터 가끔은 웃기고
가끔은 안 웃길 거야!
You feel better now?
이제 만족해?
하지만 희생이 너무 커
Yeah, but at what cost?
Six more months, three meals a day.
앞으로 6개월
하루 세 끼
내가 먹어치우는 소가
수백 마리는 될 거야
I am going to eat, like,
you know, millions of cows.
Mommy cows, daddy cows, baby cows
엄마 소, 아빠 소, 아기 소...
안돼, 아기 소는 절대 못 먹어!
No. No, I will never eat
baby cows. No veal!
Oh, but veal.
우, 송아지고기...
그건 내가 보상할게
이 고기들
What if I even things out
for you, meat-wise?
-What?
-I eat a lot of meat, right?
뭐?
- 나 고기 많이 먹지?
- 그럼
But suppose, until the baby's born,
I laid off it.
아기가 태어날 때까지
내가 고기를 끊는 거야
No extra animals would die.
You'd be eating my animals.
내 고기를 먹는 거니까
여분의 희생을 막을 수 있어
I can't believe you'd do that for me.
정말 그래줄 수 있어?
Absolutely.
I could be a vegetarian.
물론이지
채식이 뭐 별거야?
There's no meat in beer, right?
맥주엔 고기 안 들어있지?
We can still make dinner if we skip the
appetizers and ask for our check right away.
지금이라도 전채요리 건너뛰면
저녁은 먹고 나올 수 있어
기다려봐, 레이첼이 뭘
보여주려는 모양인데?
We can't go now.
Rachel is going to put on a skit.
Oh, my God!
Have you lost your mind?
내가 못살아
너 정신 나갔니?
I am finally thinking clearly.
아니, 이제야
제정신이 돌아왔어
My lucky dress wasn't working out
too well for me.
행운의 드레스는 망했지만
But for four years,
this baby never missed.
이 옷은 4년 동안
실패한 적이 없어
레이첼, 이건 안돼
Wait, I can't let
Actually, I want to see what happens.
다음 사태가 궁금하긴 하다
- 왔군요
- 네
Nice costume.
- 근사한... 의상이군요
- 네
Well, I wanted to give Emily
a big American goodbye cheer.
에밀리한테 화끈한 미국식
송별응원을 해주고 싶어서
시작할까요?
Ready. Okay.
준비! 오케이!
Give me an "E"!
- 다같이 E!
- E!
Give me an "M"!
- 다같이 M!
- M!
- 다같이 I!
- I!
Give me an "I"!
Give me an "L"!
- 다같이 L!
- L!
Give me a "Y"!
- 다같이 Y!
- Y!
What do you get?
합치면 뭐가 되죠?
오! 에밀리!
와! 에밀리! 악!
Emily! Emily!
좋아요
치어리더 레이첼, 짜잔!
That's me as a cheerleader!
괜찮아?
I loosened a tooth.
It's no big deal. I have a dentist.
이가 좀 흔들리지만
치과에 가면 돼
I'll put some ice on it.
Excuse me.
얼음 좀 대야겠어요
- 이제 나 어떡하지?
- 뭘 더하시게?
-What do I do now?
-I think you're done.
Time to take off the bra.
브라 벗을 때가 왔다
어, 아주 볼만했어요
That was really great.
But I gotta take off.
이제 정말 가봐야겠군요
Take the bra off.
브라를 벗어라...
Let's go get your coat.
- 코트 저 방에 있어요
- 네
Rachel's my girlfriend.
레이첼은 제 애인이랍니다
So this was really fun.
오늘 정말 재미있었어요
Yeah, it was real fun.
네, 자지러질 정도로
You know, this bra...
오늘따라 이 브라가...
...is really bothering me.
왜 이렇게 답답하지?
This used to be my bedroom.
여기가 내 침실이었어요
A lot of memories in here.
Lot of memories.
많은 추억이 있죠
대따 많은 추억이
If these walls could talk,
they'd say:
벽에 입이 달렸다면
이렇게 말할 걸요?
"Want to hear some memories?"
'추억을 들려주리?'
Need a hand?
- 내가 좀 도와줄까요?
- 아뇨, 혼자 할 수 있어요
I got this all under control.
You really don't seem like you do.
평소실력이 안 나오네요
God! Forget it!
젠장!
되는 게 없네!
이건 정말...
This is not how
this was supposed to happen.
이럴 생각은 아니었는데
What was supposed to happen?
그럼 어쩔 생각이었죠?
Can you not look at me
when I say this?
저쪽 보고 들을래요?
I thought that
if I could get you here...
당신을 여기로 불러들이면...
...I could seduce you.
유혹할 수 있을 것 같았어요
뭐라구요?
-Excuse me?
-Seduce you.
유혹 말이에요
유혹이라구요
I don't wear suits to work.
난 직장에서 양복을 안 입는데
당신한테서 여섯 벌이나 샀어요
And I bought six of them from you.
I'm sorry.
I thought you needed them.
죄송하네요
난 필요한 줄 알았어요
아뇨, 내가 자꾸 거길 갔던 건
당신을 보기 위해서였어요
My point is, I kept coming back
because I wanted to see you.
-Why?
-Because I like you.
- 왜요?
- 당신을 좋아하니까
You like me?
날 좋아해요?
그래요
I mean, you're beautiful
and smart and sophisticated.
레이첼은 아름답고
똑똑하고 교양 있어요
A lot of this isn't based on tonight.
오늘은 전혀 딴 사람 같지만
날 좋아한단 말이죠?
But you like me?
I can't believe this. All this time,
I liked you and you liked me!
이럴 수가, 그 동안 쭉
우리가 서로 좋아했군요
-But
-No "but."
- 하지만...
- '하지만'은 싫어요
"But" is never good. Let's leave it
at "l like you and you like me."
그냥 '우리는 서로 좋아해'
상태로 내버려두자구요
-Okay. However
-No, that's a fancy "but."
좋아요
- 그렇지만...
- '하지만'이나 그거나
My marriage, like, just ended.
난 이혼한 지 얼마 안돼서
And I'm really not ready
to get into anything yet.
당장은 어떤 것도
시도할 엄두가 안 나요
하지만?
But....
I'm sorry.
I just need a little time.
미안해요, 난 단지
시간이 좀 필요해요
Okay.
알았어요
There you are.
I was looking for you.
여기 있었네?
아까부터 찾았는데
Joshua's gone,
so you and Emily are free to go.
조슈아는 갔으니까
에밀리 데려가도 돼
It's okay.
됐어
She's still in there
enjoying her fake party.
아직도 가짜파티에
푹 빠져있어
It's too late to do
the stuff I had planned.
내 계획대로 하기엔
너무 늦었고
로스, 내가 두 사람 저녁을
완전히 망쳐놨지?
I'm sorry.
I ruined your evening.
Yeah.
맞아
If it makes you feel any better,
I made a fool of myself.
나 오늘 바보 됐으니까
조금은 위로가 되지?
Helps a little.
그건 그렇다
Is there room on that step
for a pathetic loser?
한심한 머저리가
거기 앉아도 될까?
Have a seat.
그래, 앉아
-I'm so sorry.
-It's okay.
정말 미안해
괜찮아, 어차피 시한부
데이트였는데 뭐
It was just a two-week thing anyway.
I just didn't want it
to end this way.
이렇게 끝나서 유감이지만
Or maybe you didn't want it to end.
끝내기 싫은 건 아니고?
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이야?
You seem to really like her.
진심으로 좋아하잖아
I really do.
그래, 맞아
But what am I going to do?
We agreed it'd be a two-week thing.
하지만 어쩔 거야, 둘 다
2주라는 시간에 동의했는데
No commitment.
구속은 없어
로스?
That girl just spent the entire evening
talking to your friends...
에밀리는 저녁 내내
네 친구들과 얘기하고
...asking to hear stories about you...
너에 대해서 물어보고
모니카의 사진첩을 봤어
...Iooking through
Monica's photo albums.
You don't do that
if you're just in it for two weeks.
2주 사귀고 끝낼
사람이 그러나?
You think?
- 정말?
- 그래
You've got 14 hours
until she has to be at the airport.
에밀리가 공항에 가려면
아직 14시간이나 남았는데
And you're sitting here
in a hallway...
복도에서 입술 부은 28살 짜리
치어리더랑 청승만 떨 거야?
...with a 28-year-old cheerleader
with a fat lip.
You're right.
- 네 말이 맞아
- 그럼
Thanks.
고맙다
What photo album was it?
근데 어떤 사진이었어?
I don't know. It was you
and a bunch of albino kids.
글쎄, 너하고
색소결핍증 꼬마들?
Oh, my God!
Those weren't albino kids.
돌겠네, 색소결핍증이라니!
컴퓨터 캠프에서 찍은 거야
That was computer camp!
- 얘
- 그래
-You're a pathetic loser, right?
-Oh, yeah.
- 너도 한심한 머저리지?
- 오, 그럼
Sit!
앉아
Hi.
나예요
Oh, my God. Joshua.
이런, 조슈아
Look...
저기...
...all those things I said
about not being ready
내가 아직 준비가
안됐다고 했죠?
-They're not true?
-They're all true.
- 사실이 아닌가요?
- 아뇨, 전부 사실이에요
But....
하지만...
오!
I love that "but."
그 '하지만'은 참 좋네요
Do you want to go inside
and get some coffee?
들어가서 커피 한 잔 할래요?
- 좋죠
- 그래요
Okay.
- 고마워요
- 네
Every time.
입으면 걸려들어
-What do you got there?
-Pastrami.
- 그건 뭐야?
- 파스트라미
고렇지!
-You know what goes good with that?
-Corned beef.
- 거기에 뭘 얹으면 좋게?
- 그야 절인 쇠고기지
I was going to say bologna.
But that's better.
난 볼로냐 생각했는데
그게 훨 낫겠다
- 훈제칠면조는 어때
- 좋지
-How about that smoked turkey?
-Okay.
Oh, mama!
엄마야...
-When is the baby due?
-Six months.
- 아기 언제 나와?
- 6개월 후에
If a cow died of natural causes,
I could have one of those, right?
자연사하는 소도 있는데
조금은 괜찮지 않을까?
Not if I get there first.
그것도 내 몫이야